Waco Civic Theatre records, Inclusive: 1931-2002, undated, Bulk: 1955-1995, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Audiovisual, 1958-1996, undated; 4
  - Photographs: Crimes of the Heart, 1995 March (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Photographs: Sound of Music, 1995 September (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Photographs: Annie, 1995 December (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Photographs: Nunsense II, 1996 May (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Photographs: 12 Angry Men, undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Photographs: Anastasia, undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Photographs: Barefoot in the Park, undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Photographs: Born Yesterday, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Photographs: Cheaper by the Dozen, undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Photographs: Cinderella, undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Photographs: Construction, undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Photographs: Death Trap, undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Photographs: Dial M for Murder, undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Photographs: Driving Miss Daisy, undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Photographs: The Fantasticks, undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Photographs: Goodbye, Charlie, undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Photographs: Known Productions — Snow White, Sunshine Boys, and Six Rooms, undated (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Photographs: Little Shop of Horrors, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Photographs: The Male Animal, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Photographs: Our Town, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Photographs: Plaza Suite, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Photographs: Sabrina Fair, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Photographs: South Pacific, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Photographs: Strange Bedfellows, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Photographs: Too Lewd for Publications, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Photographs: Unknown Melodramas, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Photographs: Unknown Melodramas (1), undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Photographs: Unknown Productions, undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Photographs: Unknown Productions, undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Photographs: Unknown Production (1), undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Photographs: Unknown Productions (2), undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Photographs: Unknown Productions (3,4, & 5), undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Photographs: Unknown Productions (6 & 7), undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Photographs: Unknown Production (8, 9, & 10), undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Photographs: Visit to a Small Planet, undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Photographs: Wait Until Park, undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Photographs: WCT-Children’s Theatre (1), undated (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Photographs: WCT-Children’s Theatre (2), undated (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Photographs: WCT-Known People, undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Photographs: WCT-Known People, undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Photographs: WCT “Modern” Theatre, undated (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Photographs: WCT Reception (1), undated (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Photographs: WCT Reception (2), undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Photographs: WCT-Unknown People, undated (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Photographs: WCT-Unknown People, undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Photographs: The Women, undated (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Photographs: Witness for the Prosecution, undated (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Photographs: The Wiz, undated (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Posters, undated (Drawer B 14. Folder 1)
  - Reel to Reel: untitled (1 of 2), undated (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Reel to Reel: untitled (2 of 2), undated (Box 6 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Slides: Backstage, undated (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Slides: Dracula (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 4)
  - Slides: Dracula (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 5)
  - Slides: Finishing Touches (1 of 5), undated (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 6)
  - Slides: Finishing Touches (2 of 5), undated (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - Slides: Finishing Touches (3 of 5), undated (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - Slides: Finishing Touches (4 of 5), undated (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - Slides: Finishing Touches (5 of 5), undated (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - Slides: Henry Snyder, undated (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - Slides: Night Watch, undated (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 12)
  - Slides: Nuns-Croquet (1 of 2), undated (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 13)
  - Slides: Nuns-Croquet (2 of 2), undated (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 14)
  - Slides: Nuns-Horses (1 of 2), undated (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 15)
  - Slides: Nuns-Horses (2 of 2), undated (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 16)
  - Slides: Nuns-Posed, undated (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 17)
  - Slides: Nunsmoke, undated (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 18)
  - Slides: Nunsmoke & Nuns, undated (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 19)
  - Slides: Odd Couple (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 20)
  - Slides: Odd Couple (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 21)
  - Slides: People in Black/White, undated (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 22)
  - Slides: Prisoner of 2nd Ave (1 of 2), undated (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 23)
  - Slides: Prisoner of 2nd Ave (2 of 2), undated (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 24)
  - Slides: Reluctant & Debutante, undated (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 25)
  - Slides: Scenery, undated (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 26)
  - Slides: Skin of Our Teeth, undated (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 27)
  - Slides: Six Rooms (1 of 2), undated (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 28)
  - Slides: Six Rooms (2 of 2), undated (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 29)
  - Slides: Untitled Show (1), undated (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 30)
  - Slides: Untitled Show (2), undated (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 31)
  - Slides: You Can’t Take It with You, Rosie’s Ricochet Romance & Murder at the Howard Johnson’s, undated (Box 7 OVZ, Folder 32)